ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Diaper Service Association, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Division Laundry, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Do-Wel Laundry Service Corp., 1962 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Dyckman Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and East New York Self Service Laundry, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Eastport Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Eastchester Home Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Elite Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Elite Linen Service, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Embassy Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Emergency Coat, Apron and Towel Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Empire State Cleaners, Dyers and Launderers, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Equitable Uniform Service, 1962-1963 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Erlanger's Coat, Apron and Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Essex Laundry Service, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Exchange Linen Service, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Family Laundry owners Association of New York, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Farmingdale Industrial Laundry Service, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Fayette Marine Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Fifth Avenue Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Finest Steam Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Firestone Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Fordham Industrial Rag Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Fortway Laundry Co., 1962-1963 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Freelance, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and French Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Friendly Service Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Garden City Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Garden Sanitary Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and General Diaper Service Corp., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and General Linen Supply and Laundry Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Gold Seal Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Gotham Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Grateful Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Greater New York Wet Wash Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and H.L. Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Halsey Laundry Service, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hannah's Shirt Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hayduk Linen Supply, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Heartcote Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hempstead Family Laundry Service, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hewlett Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hollis Shirt Pressing, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hollywood Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Home Linen Suppliers, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hop Wah Wet Wash Laundry, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hospital Laundry, 1962-1963 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hostess Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and House Linen Renting Service, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hub Towel Supply Co., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Hudson Superfine Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Huntington Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board I, 1962-1965 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and J&P Operating Corp., 1965 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and J&H Towel Service, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jack & Jill Diaper Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jackson Heights Shirt Laundry, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jen Sen Laundry, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Johnson's Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and The Judge Linen Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jumel Laundry, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jung Hing Laundry, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jung Sun Wet Wash, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jung Young Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board K, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and La Mar Laundry and Linen Service, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Laundered Service, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Laundry Enterprise, Inc., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Laundry Owners Association, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  Brooklyn and New York
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Laundry Processors Corp., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Lavender Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Lawrence Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Leewood Carlton Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mme Lerner's Hand, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Light Steam Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Linen Service Council of New Jersey, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Linens of the Week, Inc., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Lion Laundry Service, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Little Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Lomac Steam Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Long Island Laundrymen's Association, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Lou Ena Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and M&D Laundry Co., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and M.&M. Laundry, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Maling Laundry, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Manhasset Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Manhattan C&A, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Master Coat, Apron and Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mayfair Cleaners and Launderers, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mayrod T.S. Co., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Medical Arts Linen Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Menehan Laundry, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mercury Uniform Rental Service, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Metropolitan Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Modern Silver Linen Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Modern Way Shirt Pressing Corp., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Morgan Linen Service, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mount Kisco Laundry and Dry Cleaners Corp., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Mutual Kings Coat and Apron Supply, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and National Coat, Apron and Linen Supply, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Neighborhood Laundry, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Amsterdam Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Home Town Laundry and Cleaning Co., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Method Coat and Apron, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Method Service Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Modern Wet Wash, Inc., 1962 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Newtown Wash Service Corp., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New Union C & A, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New York Butchers Coat and Apron Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New York Globe Laundry, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and New York Hand Laundrymen's Association, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Nickel Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Norwood Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Nu R&S Laundry Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board O, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and P.M. Laundry, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pacific Laundry Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pan American Linen Supply, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Par-X-Uniform Service Corp., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Patton Laundry, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Peerless Linen Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Peerless Coat and Apron Supply, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pelham Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pennsylvania Coat and Apron Supply, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Perfect Coat and Apron, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Personal Laundry, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Personal Linen Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Philmar Coat and Apron Supply, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pilgrim Laundry, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pioneer Laundry Service Corp., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Polo Coat and Apron Supply, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Pondfield Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Premier Essex Linen Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Premier Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Primwood Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Princeton Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Professional Linen Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Progressive Laundry, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Prosperity Shirt Laundry, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Prudential Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Puritan Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board Q, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and R.F.R. Uniform Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Raud, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rebann Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Reliable Coat, Apron and Towel Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Reliable Uniport Laundry Co., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rex Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rhum Corp - Gould Laundry, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Riteway Laundry Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Riverdale Laundry, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Riverside Coat, Apron, Towel and Linen Supply and Laundry, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Roamer Linen Supply, Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Roamer Steam Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rockaway Park International, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rose Towel and Linen, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Royal Coat and Apron, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rubin's Coat and Apron Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Ruth's Home Laundry, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Rye Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sanitex Towel Service, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Scarsdale Hand Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Seltzer's Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sheldon Faster, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Signal Coat and Apron Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sparco Steam Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Square Deal Laundry Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Standard Coat and Apron, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Star Napkin and Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Starlight Laundry, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and State Overall Service, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and St. Edmund's Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sterlized Diaper Service, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Suffolk Shirt Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sun Ar Wet Wash, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sunshine Quaker Laundry Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Superb Towel Supply, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Supreme Laundry, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Swan Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sweetheart Laundry Co., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Swift Laundry, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Swiss Launderers, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Taylor's Hand Laundry, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Textene Laundries, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Thomas Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Terminal Steam Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Tip-Top Laundry, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Tippy Hotel Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Towel Delivery Corp., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Towel Service Bureau, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Towel Supply Corp., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Town and Village Laundry, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Town Cleaners, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Truesdale Laundry Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Tudor Laundry Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board U, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board V, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wan Kiu Wet Wash Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wallach Utility Laundry, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Walter's South Side, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Washington Heights Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Webster Steam Laundry Co., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wellworth Laundry Service, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and White Mountain Laundry, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wholesale Hand Laundry Service, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wholesale Laundry Board of Trade, Inc., 1962 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wholesale Shirt Laundries, Inc., 1962 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Williamsburg Coat, Apron and Towel Supply Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Willis Valet Service, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Wing Gong Laundry, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Winthrop Laundry Corp., 1962 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and White Plains Coat, Apron and Supply Co., 1962 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board X-Z, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board Master Contract, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and ABK Service Corp (Ace), 1966 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and A&F Steam Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Allen Diaper Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Allied Laundry Co., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Allstate Linen Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and All Star Shirt Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and American Linen Supply Co., 1966-1972 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Asia Wet Wash Laundry Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Auburn Towel Service, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board B, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Cadet Linen Service Corp., 1966 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Century Linen Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Chelsea Towel Service, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Clover Laundry, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Clifton Coat and Apron Supply Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Commercial St. Edmund's Laundry Corp., 1966 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Consolidated Laundries Corp., 1966 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Crown Linen Service, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board D-E, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board F-G, 1966-1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board H, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board I, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board J.D.J. Cleaners Corp., 1974 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and J&H Towel, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jack & Jill Diaper Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jen Sen Shirt Pressing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jung Hing Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Jung Sun Wet Wash Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board K, 1966-1976 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board Light Steam Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Light Steam Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Linens of the Week, Inc., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board and Long Island Hand Laundrymen's Association, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 13)